<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
  id="pvr.fortherecord.argus"
  version="1.0.150.143"
  name="ForTheRecord PVR client"
  provider-name="Fred Hoogduin, Marcel Groothuis">
  <requires>
    <c-pluff version="0.1"/>
  </requires>
  <extension
    point="xbmc.pvrclient"
    library_linux="XBMC_ForTheRecord.pvr"
    library_osx="XBMC_ForTheRecord.pvr"
    library_wingl="XBMC_ForTheRecord_win32.pvr"
    library_windx="XBMC_ForTheRecord_win32.pvr"
    library_android="libXBMC_ForTheRecord.so"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="be">XBMC frontend for the ForTheRecord PVR http://www.4therecord.eu/</summary>
    <summary lang="cs">Rozhraní XBMC pro ForTheRecord PVR http://www.4therecord.eu/</summary>
    <summary lang="da">XBMC frontend til ForTheRecord PVR http://www.4therecord.eu/</summary>
    <summary lang="de">XBMC-Frontend für den ForTheRecord-PVR http://www.4therecord.eu/</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Frontend του XBMC για το ForTheRecord PVR http://www.4therecord.eu/</summary>
    <summary lang="en">XBMC frontend for the ForTheRecord PVR http://www.4therecord.eu/</summary>
    <summary lang="es">XBMC frontend para ForTheRecord  PVR http://www.4therecord.eu/</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">XBMC frontend para ForTheRecord PVR http://www.4therecord.eu/</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Interface logicielle XBMC pour l'enregistreur vidéo ForTheRecord http://www.4therecord.eu/</summary>
    <summary lang="he">ממשק משתמש לXBMC עבור ForTheRecord PVR http://www.4therecord.eu/</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">XBMC frontend a ForTheRecord PVR szerverhez. http://www.4therecord.eu/</summary>
    <summary lang="it">Frontend di XBMC per il PVR ForTheRecord http://www.4therecord.eu/</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">ForTheRecord PVR http://www.4therecord.eu/ 을 위한 XBMC 프론트엔드</summary>
    <summary lang="lt">XBMC sąsaja ForTheRecord PVR http://www.4therecord.eu/</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Interfejs XBMC dla ForTheRecord PVR http://www.4therecord.eu/</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">XBMC frontend para o ForTheRecord PVR http://www.4therecord.eu/</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">XBMC frontend para o ForTheRecord PVR http://www.4therecord.eu/</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">XBMC фронтэнд для ForTheRecord PVR http://www.4therecord.eu/</summary>
    <summary lang="sk">Rozhranie XBMC pre ForTheRecord PVR http://www.4therecord.eu/</summary>
    <summary lang="sl">XBMC-jev vmesnik za ForTheRecord PVR http://www.4therecord.eu/</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">XBMC frontend för ForTheRecord PVR http://www.4therecord.eu/</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">XBMC的ForTheRecord PVR前端  http://www.4therecord.eu/</summary>
    <description lang="be">ForTheRecord PVR frontend. Supports streaming of Live TV &amp; Recordings, listening to Radio channels, EPG and schedules.</description>
    <description lang="cs">Rozhraní ForTheRecord PVR. Podporuje proudové vysílání živého vysílání a nahrávek, poslech kanálů rádia, EPG, a časovače.</description>
    <description lang="da">ForTheRecord PVR frontend; understøtter streaming af TV &amp; optagelser, Radio kanaler, EPG og tidsplaner.</description>
    <description lang="de">Erlaubt die Wiedergabe von Live TV und Aufnahmen mittels ForTheRecord-PVR auf XBMC. Desweiteren werden Radio-Kanäle, EPG und Zeitpläne unterstützt.</description>
    <description lang="el">Frontend για το ForTheRecord PVR. Υποστηρίζει ροές Live TV &amp; Εγγραφές, ακρόαση Ραδιοφώνου, EPG και προγραμματισμό.</description>
    <description lang="en">ForTheRecord PVR frontend. Supports streaming of Live TV &amp; Recordings, listening to Radio channels, EPG and schedules.</description>
    <description lang="es">ForTheRecord PVR frontend. Soporta reproducción en vivo, grabación, canales de radio, EPG y calendarios.</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">ForTheRecord PVR frontend. Soporta reproducción en vivo, grabación, canales de radio, EPG y calendarios.</description>
    <description lang="fr">Interface logicielle pour l'enregistreur vidéo ForTheRecord. Supporte la lecture en continu de direct télévision et son enregistrement, l'écoute de radios, les guides de programmes et les minuteries.</description>
    <description lang="he">ממשק משתמש ForTheRecord PVR . תומך בצפייה בשידורי טלוויזיה חיים והקלטות, רשימות ערוצי רדיו,ולחות שידורים.</description>
    <description lang="hu">ForTheRecord frontend. Élő adások, felvételek és rádió csatornák sugárzásának támogatása EPG-vel és időzítéssel</description>
    <description lang="it">Frontend PVR ForTheRecord. Supporta lo streaming della TV Live e registrazioni, ascolto di canali radio, EPG e programmazione.</description>
    <description lang="ko">ForTheRecord PVR 프론트엔드. TV 시정 &amp; 녹화, 라디오 채널 청취, EPG, 예약 지원</description>
    <description lang="lt">ForTheRecord PVR sąsaja. Palaiko transliaciją Live TV &amp; įrašus, klausytis radijo kanalus, EPG ir tvarkaraščius</description>
    <description lang="nl">ForTheRecord PVR frontend. Ondersteunt het bekijken van Live TV en opnames, het beluisteren van radio zenders, het tonen van de EPG en het inplannen/beheren van nieuwe opnames (Timers).</description>
    <description lang="pl">Interfejs ForTheRecord PVR. Wspiera strumieniowanie TV na żywo i nagrywanie, słuchanie radia, EPG i harmonogramy.</description>
    <description lang="pt">ForTheRecord PVR frontend. Suporta streaming de Live TV &amp; Gravação, ouvir  estações de rádio, EPG e agendamentos.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Frontend PVR ForTheRecord. Suporta streaming de TV ao Vivo &amp; Gravações, escutar canais de rádio, EPG e agendamentos.</description>
    <description lang="ru">Фронтэнд ForTheRecord PVR. Поддерживает потоковое TV, запись, прослушивание радио-каналов, ЕПГ и расписания.</description>
    <description lang="sk">Rozhranie pre ForTheRecord PVR. Je podporované streamovanie živého televízneho vysielania a nahrávok, počúvanie rozhlasových staníc, EPG a časovače.</description>
    <description lang="sl">Vmesnik za ForTheRecord PVR; podpira pretakanje televizije v živo &amp; posnetkov, poslušanje radia, EPG in spored.</description>
    <description lang="sv">ForTheRecord PVR frontend; Stödjer strömning av direktsänd TV &amp; inspelningar, lyssna på radiokanaler, EPG och schemaläggning.</description>
    <description lang="zh">ForTheRecord PVR前端，支持直播电视播放和录制、收听电台、电子节目单和日程表</description>
    <disclaimer lang="be">This is unstable software! The authors are in no way responsible for failed recordings, incorrect timers, wasted hours, or any other undesirable effects..</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="cs">Tento software není stabilní. Autoři nejsou žádným způsobem zodpovědní za selhání při nahrávání, neplatné časovače, ztracený čas, či jakékoliv jiné nežádoucí události...</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="da">Dette er ustabilt software! Ophavsmændene er på ingen måde ansvarlige for fejlede optagelser, fejlagtige timere, spildte timer, eller andre uønskede konsekvenser..</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="de">Diese Software ist noch in der Entwicklung! Die Autoren sind nicht für fehlgeschlagene Aufnahmen, falsche Timer, verschwendete Zeit oder andere ungewollte Effekte verantwortlich.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="el">Ασταθές πρόγραμμα! Οι δημιουργοί δεν είναι σε καμία περίπτωση υπεύθυνοι για αποτυχημένες εγγραφές, λανθασμένους χρονοδιακόπτες, χαμένες ώρες, ή κάθε είδους ανεπιθύμητα αποτελέσματα..</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en">This is unstable software! The authors are in no way responsible for failed recordings, incorrect timers, wasted hours, or any other undesirable effects..</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="es">¡Este es un software inestable! Los autores no son de ninguna manera responsables de las grabaciones fallidas o incorrectas, las temporizadores perdidas, ni otros efectos no deseables..</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="es_AR">¡Este software es inestable! Los autores no se responsabilizan por grabaciones fallidas, temporizadores incorrectos, horas perdidas, o cualquier otro efecto no deseado..</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="es_MX">¡Esto es software inestable! Los autores no son de ninguna manera responsables por grabaciones fallidas, temporizadores incorrectos, horas perdidas o cualquier otro efecto no deseado...</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="fr">Cette interface est instable ! Les auteurs ne sont pas responsables de l'échec des enregistrements, des minuteries erronées, du temps perdu et autres effets indésirables..</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="hu">Ez nem stabil szoftver! A készítők nem vállalnak felelősséget, a hibás felvételért, rossz időzítésért, elvesztegetett időért...</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="it">Questo software non è stabile! Gli autori non sono in alcun modo responsabili per registrazioni fallite, programmazioni non corrette, ore perse o altri effetti indesiderati.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ko">이 소프트웨어는 불안정합니다! 제작자는 녹화 실패, 부정확한 타이머, 시간 낭비 및 기타 예상하지 못한 결과에 대해 책임지지 않습니다..</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="lt">Tai yra nestabili programinė įranga! Autorius jokiu būdu neatsakingas už nepavykusius įrašus, neteisingus laikmačius, iššvaistytas valandas, ar nutikus kitiems nepageidaujamiems poveikiams ...[COLOR=red](xbmc.lt siūlo/rekomenduoja testuojant šį priedą persijungti į Anglų [orinali] kalbą)[/COLOR]</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="mk">Ова е нестабилен софтвер! Авторите на ниту еден начин не одговараат за неуспешни снимки, неточни тајмери, потрошени часови, или било кои други несакани ефекти.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pl">To oprogramowanie jest niestabilne! Autorzy w żaden sposób nie odpowiadają za nieudane nagrania, źle działające wyłączniki czasowe, stracone godziny czy też jakiekolwiek inne niepożądane efekty.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pt">Este é um software instável! Os autores não se responsabilizam por falhas nas gravações, temporizadores incorrectos, horas perdidas ou outro qualquer efeito não desejado...</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Este software é instável! Os autores não se responsabilizam por falhas de gravações, agendamentos incorretos, horas perdidas, ou outros efeitos indesejáveis.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ru">Это тестовая программа! Авторы не несут никакой ответственности за испорченные записи, неверные таймеры, потраченное время и прочие нежелательные эффекты.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="sk">Tento softvér nie je stabilný! Autori nenesú žiadnu zodpovednosť za chybné nahrávky vysielania, nesprávne časovače alebo iné neželané udalosti spôsobené týmto softvérom..</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="sl">To je nestabilna programska oprema! Avtorji niso odgovorni za neuspela snemanja, nepravilne časovnike, zapravljen čas in katerikoli drug neželen učinek...</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="sv">Detta är ostabil mjukvara! Upphovsmännen är inte ansvariga för misslyckade inspelningar, inkorrekta timers, bortslösade timmar, eller några andra oönskade effekter..</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="zh">这是不稳定版的软件！作者不对录制失败、错误定时造成时间浪费或其它不良影响负责。</disclaimer>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

